[Music]
Used to cruise on weekends, friends on
the beach. Now frustrated drivers fill
every side street. What once was a
shortcut is a nightmare now. All for a
ribbon and a political vow.
Proposition K
got it wrong all along. We're so on the
traffic as a parade rolls on. Cut off
our face to build their outdoor sts
and wings are burning with rain.
[Music]
Too loud, too fast, can't sleep, can't
last.
[Music]
[Applause]
Once we had peace off the great highway,
now it's gridlock on Tuesday, honking
every day. Cardio smile called it
progress for all but hundreds of
neighbors ignore his recall. No
environmental
study to say if we're doomed
just by stand the blocks and another
ballot consumed.
Proposition K
got done got it wrong all along. We're
soaking on the traffic as a parade rolls
on. cut off our face to build their
outdoor state. Sunset enrichment are
burning with
[Music]
Too loud too fast asleep can last.